sprungup.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy | SprungUp.com

Privacy Policy for sprungup.com 

If you want more information or have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by e-mail to webmaster@sprungup.com.

Sprungup.com in the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by sprungup.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites sprungup.com makes use of log files. The information in the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), analyze date / time you are on the sides / exit, and the number of clicks to trends, to administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other information are not limited to information that personally identifies you.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
sprungup.com uses cookies to information about visitors preferences, record specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors save browser type or any other information that the visitor sends via the browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on sprungup.com.  
• Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to advertise to people on their visit to sprungup.com and other sites on the Internet are based.  
• Users can disable the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following address - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense 

These third party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on sprungup.com directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by third party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or the advertising content you see to personalize.

SprungUp.com has no access or control over these cookies that are used by third parties for marketing purposes.

You should discuss the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices to be consulted. Privacy sprungup.com 's does not apply to, and we can not control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you can do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with Web browser, you can find on the websites of the respective browser.
